Wildey "Bud" Kimball Photographs 1959-1980
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- 9"x9" color aerial transparencies and negatives arranged by subject alphabetically, 7
  - Unidentified aerials, negatives (Box-folder 8/164-166)
  - Unidentified aerials, transparencies (Box-folder 8/167)
  - Widoo, color transparencies (Box-folder 8/168)
- Miscellaneous negatives and transparencies, 8
  - Includes aerials and non aerials, infrared false color, airplanes, Seattle International Raceways, etc, 35 mm color negative. (Box-folder 9/169)
  - Non-aerials of Seattle International Raceways, 35 mm unmounted color transparencies. (Box-folder 9/170)
  - Aerials of Seattle night skyline, 2 1/4" unmounted color transparencies. (Box-folder 9/171)
  - Columbia River Bar (3), Mt. Rainier and Mt. Adams (2), unidentified (3), 2 1/4"x10" panorama color transparencies. (Box-folder 9/172)
- Microfiche: Mt. St. Helens, 5"x4 1/4" color aerial transparencies, 9
  Each fiche contains a listing of what is on the fiche, followed by 70 images. Selected 5"x4 1/4" color aerial transparencies are present for fiches 04-07.
  - Microfiche guides (7); Handwritten keys to fiche 01-02 (7 pages); Printed listings to fiche 01-07, from fiche (7 pages) (Box-folder 10/173)
  - Fiche 04, May 3, 1980, May 17, 1980, June 15 1980, June 20 1980 (Box-folder 10/174)
  - Fiche 05, June 20 1980 (Box-folder 10/175)
  - Fiche 06, July 28 1980, August 3 1980, August 30 1980 (Box-folder 10/176)
  - Fiche 07, August 30 1980 (Box-folder 10/177)
- 5"x4 1/4" color aerial transparencies, and miscellany, 10
  - Alaska. Northway, Palmer, Prince William Sound; Meares, Harriman, Columbia, Knik, Colony, Harvard, Matanuska, Tazlina, Bremner, Chitistine, Chisana, Bow Pass Glaciers, September 1972 (Box-folder 11/178)
  - Alaska. Includes Columbia, Compton, Being, Neary, Malaspina, Marjorie Glaciers; Icy Bay, 1978 (Box-folder 11/179)
  - Mt. St. Helens (and area). Mostly eruption aftermath, May/June, 1980 (Box-folder 11/180)
  - Washington Irrigation Co., Centralia, WA. Mine Recovery, June 20 1980 (Box-folder 11/181)
  - Newspaper clippings which print Kimball photos (20) (Box-folder 11/182)
    Also 2 color separations for newspaper printing
  - Biographical information, 1965 (Box-folder 11/183)
- Color prints arranged alphabetically by area, 11
  - Bremerton infrared aerials (Box-folder 12/184)
  - Building at Auburn cutoff from I-5 (Box-folder 12/185)
  - Cowlitz Dam and vicinity (Box-folder 12/186)
  - D.O.E. Thurston (Box-folder 12/187)
  - Lower Cushman (Box-folder 12/188)
  - Makah Indian Reservation (Box-folder 12/189)
  - Olympia (Box-folder 12/190)
  - Quinault Indian Reservation (Box-folder 12/191)
  - Ruby Creek fire-infrared aerial (Box-folder 12/192)
  - Seashore (Box-folder 12/193)
  - Seattle (Box-folder 12/194)
  - Steilacoom infrared aerials (Box-folder 12/194)
  - Tacoma (Box-folder 12/196)
  - Unidentified aerials (Box-folder 12/197)
  - Unidentified infrared aerials (Box-folder 12/198)
  - Widoo (Box-folder 12/199)
  - Miscellaneous non-aerial color prints including airplanes and aerial photo equipment, commercial establishments, mountains, seascapes, Boeing Field control tower, etc (Box-folder 12/200)
- Rolls of 7" B&W, color or infrared negative aerial negatives, 12
  - (Box-roll 13/201)
    4/1/1966 2 Tacoma Mall; 4/1/1966 9 Tacoma Mall; 9/2/1968 32 Brown's Point; 9/2/1968 44 Port of Tacoma; 5 feet of unnumbered negatives including Cascade Mountains, Snoqualmie Pass, Tacoma, tanker ship at dock; 5/17/1968 1 Residential' 5/17/1968 2 Port of Tacoma; 5 feet of unnumbered negatives of industrial areas. Tacoma Tideflats(?) Weyerhaeuser (?); 7/30/1968 90,95 Gig Harbor; 7/30/1968 86,89 Point Defiance, North Tacoma; 7/30/1968 81,83 Tacoma Narrows Bridge, North Tacoma; 3/11/1969 134,158 Downtown Tacoma; 10 feet of unnumbered negatives of Tacoma Narrows Bridge and vicinity
  - (Box-roll 13/202)
    5 feet of a small lake; 15 feet of large river valley; 20 feet of unidentified forest and water; 7 feet of unidentified lake; 10 feet of Puget Sound beach (?)
  - (Box-roll 13/203)
    5/1/1968 1-3 Mountains; 4 Bridge construction; 5 WSU campus; 8 Mountains
  - (Box-roll 13/204)
    12/1/1967 1-79 Mt. Rainier; 7/17/1968 1-4 unidentified Olympia Brewery; 7,8,12-15,18 Public access to lake behind Cowlitz Dam; 20-22,24-26 Highway and bridge near dam; 36,38,39,41,42,44,45 Fish hatchery near dam; 29-32 Cowlitz Dam; 47-49 Residential; 52 Trailer court
  - (Box-roll 13/205)
    3/10/1969 1-44 Gig Harbor and vicinity; 9/2/1968 1-31 Unidentified residential area on sound or lake
  - (Box-roll 13/206)
    4/2/1966 1-13 Tacoma
  - (Box-roll 14/207)
    12/16/1967 1-28 Tacoma Mall
  - (Box-roll 14/208)
    2/16/1967 1-6,8,9,11-14,16-19,21,23,26-40,42-46,48-71 Tacoma; 10 feet Tacoma; 6 feet Port of Tacoma
  - (Box-roll 14/209)
    7/27/1968 1-5 Unidentified; 15-18 Cowlitz Lake; 24-35 unidentified community; 7/30/1968 18-31 Tacoma-Westgate; 32-36 Port of Tacoma; 39-45 Brown's; 46-54,56-77 Port of Tacoma
  - (Box-roll 14/210)
    3/11/1969 162-166 Port of Tacoma
  - (Box-roll 14/211)
    7/30/1968 96-101 Oswald Airport, Tacoma
  - (Box-roll 14/212)
    3/11/1969 100-106 Bremerton; 108-109 Unidentified marina; 111-119 Bremerton; 120,122-123,125-129 Gig Harbor and vicinity; 130-133 Bremerton
  - Taken 1973-1974 (Box-roll 14/213)
    Includes Puyallup Fairgrounds, City of Tacoma waterway, Whey. airport.
  - Taken 1975-1976 (Box-roll 14/214)
    18 feet Tacoma; 5 feet Tacoma waterway; 20 feet unidentified; 7 feet Chambers Creek, Tacoma (print in container 5, Tacoma); 22 feet Roy, Washington
  - (Box-roll 15/215)
    8 feet Tacoma(?); 18 feet Chambers Creek and vicinity; 1 foot Logged area; 1 foot Puyallup Fairgrounds; 16 feet Tacoma waterfront and downtown; 5 feet Gig Harbor
  - (Box-roll 15/216)
    9 feet Unidentified; 5 feet Airport; 4 feet Goodyear Blimp; 4 feet Centralia-Chehalis Airport; 5 feet Goodyear blimp; 6 feet Unidentified; 14 feet Steilacoom (6/23/1974); Also included (according to list on roll) but not confirmed: Jump airport, Casper; Blakley Island (7/20/1974); Muckleshoot (5/21/1974-7/24/1974); Weyerhaeuser airport; Infrared aerials Steilacoom (5/12/1974)
  - (Box-roll 15/217)
    Makah Indian Reservation rejects; Tatoosh Island
  - (Box-roll 15/218)
    According to list on roll this includes: Miscellaneous (1972-1973); Rejects from Tacoma Public Utility Port Orchard Airport; Gig Harbor verticals; Log booms; Bill and Dots; Misc. Steilacoom; Thunderbird; Charles Roger School; 19th and Bridgeport, Tacoma; Point Defiance Park; Yacht Club; Smelter; Downtown Tacoma; Island; Olympia Port and Capitol; Olympia Brewery; Cowlitz Dam; Fisheries; Bridges; Hoskins; Panorama City; Steilacoom
  - (Box-roll 15/219)
    List on roll: SeaTac; Doug's home; Chehalis Airport; Olympia Airport; Golf courses; Panarama City; Steilacoom verticals; Western State Hospital; Evergreen Airport; Marine View Drive; Orange Tide; Rocky Point; Lakes near home; Day Island; Narrows Bridge; Purdy; Marine View Drive- tide in; Concrete Tech; Smelter; Cox (7/2/1973); Herron Island; Fish pen- Squaxin Island; Olympia Red Tide; Cox; Marine View Drive- tide out; City of Steilacoom; Belfair; Gig Harbor; Port of Tacoma; Puyallup; Sumner; Orting; Eatonville; Morton; Mineral
  - (Box-roll 15/220)
    (missing 2-1-2005). Makah Indian Reservation; Neah Bay
  - (Box-roll 15/221)
    Miscellaneous unidentified (1975)
  - (Box-roll 16/222)
    Quinault Indian Reservation (4/13-14/1974)
  - (Box-roll 16/223)
    1972 verticals, unidentified
  - (Box-roll 16/224)
    vertical rejects (1975-1976)
  - (Box-roll 16/225)
    1973 verticals; Tacoma color negatives; Sea-Tac; Seattle-color and infrared negatives
  - (Box-roll 16/226)
    unidentified.
  - (Box-roll 16/227)
  - (Box-roll 16/228)
    May 17 1980 Mt. St. Helens
  - (Box-roll 16/229)
    Riffe Lake; Mossyrock Dam; Bridge; Cowlitz River (10/15/1972)
  - (Box-roll 17/230)
    October 15 1972 Olympia Brewery; Drive-in; State Capitol; downtown Olympia; Tacoma; Pt. Defiance; "Cheney Studs" lumber yard (1/4/1973); power line survey; Gig Harbor (2/4/1973); Undated. Unidentified river channel; Undated Shelton, WA; Undated. Unidentified infrareds
  - undated (Box-roll 17/231)
    Unidentified aerial surveys; "Rejects" (4/30/1976); Grays Harbor "D.O.E." (5/26/1977)
  - undated (Box-roll 17/232)
    Unidentified city blocks; river course
  - September 17 1980 (Box-roll 17/233)
    Mt. Hood. OR
  - undated (Box-roll 17/234)
    Unidentified aerial surveys
  - undated (Box-roll 17/235)
    Unidentified aerial surveys. Includes Chehalis Steam Plant (?)
  - undated (Box-roll 17/236)
    Unidentified "test strips": airport runway
  - undated (Box-roll 17/237)
    Aerial surveys, labeled "Washington irrigation"
  - undated (Box-roll 17/238)
    Unidentified aerial surveys: creek path. Possibly continuation of Roll 37.
- Oversize Prints, 13
  - B&W prints- fashion, construction etc (Box oversize)
  - B&W aerial prints (Box oversize)
  - B&W aerial transparency (Box oversize)
  - Color aerial prints-includes Seattle, Tacoma and Olympia (Box oversize)
  - Color transparency (Box oversize)
  - Miscellaneous color prints-includes nature, fashion, commercial buildings, etc (Box oversize)